A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Quarterly; Review FA939
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Quarterly; Review
1957-1968
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University Press
FA939
4.4 Cubic Feet 10 boxes.
10 boxes.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Separated Materials
3 volume set is available at the RU archives campus office.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for scholarly research.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 534
Medical sciences; Science -- Study and teaching; Medical technology; Medicine, Preventive; Medical education; Biology -- Research; Life sciences; Medical research; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Rockefeller University Press
- Rockefeller Institute quarterly, v. 1-6, 1957-1962 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents note
  23 pamphlets complete includes v. 1, no. 3 (September 1957) issued 2 ways.
  Biographical / Historical
  Superseded by Rockefeller Institute review.
- Rockefeller Institute review. v. 1-3, no. 2, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
  12 pamphlets complete.
  Continued as Rockefeller University review.
  - v. 1 1-4, 1963
  - v. 2 1-6, 1964
  - v. 3 1-2, 1965
- Rockefeller University review. v. 3, no. 3- v. 6, no. 3, 1965-1968 (Box 1)
  17 pamphlets complete
  Ceased publication after this volume.
  - v. 3 no. 3-6, 1965
  - v. 4 no. 1-5 (July/August not issued), 1966
  - v. 5 no. 1-5, 1967
  - v. 6 no. 1-3, 1968
- Photographs (some negatives), drawings (some original), layouts and other kinds of artwork used in Quarterly and Review, 1957-1968 (Box 3, Box 4, Box 2)
  Contains some unidentified items and also a group of materials which were prepared and worked on but which were never published.
  v. 5, no. 1 (1967) and v. 6, no. 2 (1968) missing.
  See Box 1 for complete set of the publication.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  Date received or inventoried: January 1978
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in groups by volumes and issue number and tied in bundles by year.
- Duplicate copies
  - 1957-1961 (Box 5)
  - 1962-1964 (Box 6)
  - 1965-1966 I (Box 7)
  - 1966 II-1967 I (Box 8)
  - 1967 II (Box 9)
  - 1968 (Box 10)